http://www.newreflectionscounseling.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are
Owner and Data Controller
New Reflections Counseling, Inc. (NRC)
267 Regency Ridge Dr., Dayton, Ohio 45459
937-396-7077
Websites
NRC owns and operates several websites, which we use to provide you our services:
Statement of Acceptance of Our Privacy Policy
Use of NRC’s websites and their features and services constitutes your acceptance of our privacy policy.
If you ever wish to opt-out, please unsubscribe from our services. If automatic unsubscription fails for some reason, you can contact us via phone, postal mail, or online contact (see above for contact details).
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
When you sign up for a course, free gift, or other information, your contact information is stored with Get Response (getresponse.com). We will continue to provide the services and information you requested until you tell us otherwise.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
General data about use of this website is stored with Google.
Who we share your data with
We don’t share your data with anyone (other than to store it and view it ourselves).
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
If you are a client of ours, then your personal contact information is transported to our servers through encryption (SSL). We store contact and appointment information. We do not store clinical information.
Additional information
Further details regarding our privacy policy.
How we protect your data
If you are a client of ours, then your personal contact information is transported to our servers through encryption (SSL). We store contact and appointment information. We do not store clinical information.
What data breach procedures we have in place
Our hosting provider provides our security.
What third parties we receive data from
N/A
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
N/A
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
All of your personal data is considered confidential and is protected and treated as such.
Recent Posts
COVID-19 (Novel Coronavirus)
Introvert Believer Conference 2020
MBTI® Personality Assessment
Group Counseling
Why New Reflections Counseling?
Search
Browse Categories
Counselors (15)
Counselor Comments (6)
Matt Pavlik (15)
FAQs (15)
Help With (17)
Identity (9)
Marriage (7)
Single (3)
Trauma (6)
News (3)
Resources (1)
